David E. Lilienthal Papers, 1900-1981 (bulk 1950-1981 ): Inventory MC148
EADs for public policy collection from import batch
- Series 18: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1905 October 19-1981; 208 boxes; 2 items
  - Subseries 18I: 1967-1968, 15 boxes
    - Connecticut River Volley, Anti-Pollution League, 1968; 1 box (Box 474)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1968; 1 box (Box 474)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1968; 1 box (Box 474)
    - Cousins, Norman, 1968; 1 box (Box 474)
    - Daggett, John T, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Daniels, Jonathan, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Davison, Peter, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - DePauw University, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Dillon, Douglas, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Dix, William S, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Doar, John, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Drabkin, Mrs. Israel, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Dukes County Historical Society, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Eccles, Marriner S, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Educational Broadcasting Corporation, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Education and World Affairs, Inc. (EWA), 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Engelhard Minerals and Chemicals Corporation, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Farmanfarmaian, Khodadad, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Federal Professional Association, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Feis, Herbert, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Ferren, John M, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - First National Bank of Oregon, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Flom, Joseph H, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Fortas, Abe, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Fowler, Henry H, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Franklin Book Programs, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Freedom House, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Fugitt, Warren G, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1968; 1 box (Box 475)
    - Galantiere, Lewis, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Garces Cordoba, Bernardo, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Garces Giraldo, Diego, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Gardner, John W, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Geraghty, James M, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Glennan, T. Keith, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Glick, Frank and Virginia, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Goheen, Robert F, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Greenbaum, Edward S, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Greene, Mrs. Nathan, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Grim, Ralph E, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Gullion, Edmund A, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Hannah, John A, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Harvard Business Review, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Harvard Law School, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Hearst, William Randolph Jr, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Heffner, Richard D, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Hill, Lister, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Hough, Henry B, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Hughes, Richard J, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Illinois, University of, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Re India, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Re Indonesia, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Institute on Man and Science, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Institute for Mediterranean Affairs, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Institute of Public Administration, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - International Exchange Program, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Iowa, University of, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Re Iran, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Re Iran Emergency Reconstruction and Rehabilitation Committee, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Iran Foundation, Inc, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Re Ivory Coast, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Jackson, Barbara, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Re "Jamaica Program for Aviation Training" (in New York), 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Javits, Jacob K, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Johnson, Joseph E, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Johnson, U. Alexis, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Jones, Thomas R, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Katzenbach, Nicholas deB, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Keio University, Tokyo, Japan, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Kennedy, Robert F, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Klein, Anna, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - Kuralt, Charles, 1968; 1 box (Box 476)
    - League of Women Voters, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Leonhart, William, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Levin, Gerald M, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Lilienthal, Allen, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Lilienthal, Allen Jr, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Lilienthal, David E. III, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Lindsay, John V, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Lively, Robert A, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - McAlister, John T., Jr, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - McCloy, John J, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - McGovern, George, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - McGraw-Hill, Inc, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - McNamara, Robert S, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Macy, John W. Jr, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Marist College, Poughkeepsie, New York, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Re Martha's Vineyard, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Marton, Andrew, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - McKitterick, Nathaniel M, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Mead, Thomas A, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Michigan State University, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Middle Tennessee State University, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Miller, Mark I, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Monroney, A.S. Mike, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Morehouse, Edward W, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Morgan, Lucy S, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Morino, Mitsutoshi, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Murphy, Franklin D, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - NAACP Special Contribution Fund, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Nwito, Mrs. Shinako, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Nathan, Robert R, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - National Academy of Public Administration, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - National Rural Electric Cooperative Association, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Nebraska, University of, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - New School for Social Research, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - New York University, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Newsweek, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Re Nixon, Richard M, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Re Nuclear Power Plant, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Nugent, Luci Johnson, 1968; 1 box (Box 477)
    - Oakes, John B, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Overseas Decelopment Council (ODC), 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Owen, Marguerite, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Penalosa Camargo, Enrique, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Pepperdine College, Los Angeles, California, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Perkins, James A, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Philip, Nicholas W, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Pike, Sumner T, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Planned Parenthood/World Population, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - President's Commission on Postal Organization, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Re Princeton University, 1968; 1 box
      - Princeton University Press, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Re Publications by David E. Lilienthal, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
      Includes Management: A Humanist Art, 1968.
    - Re Puerto Rico, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Radcliffe College, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - RAI Corporation, Italian Radio TV System, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Random House, Tnc, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Reston, James, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Rickover, Hyman G, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Robock, Stefan H, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Rockefeller, John D. III, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. - Birthday Memorial Committee, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. III, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Rosenak, Bernard, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Rouhani, Mansour, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Sachs., Alexander, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - St. Lawrence, Lee, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E, 1968; 1 box (Box 478)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Schmidt, Benno C, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Schwartz, David, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Sen, Sudhir, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Shahmirzadi, Hassan, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Sholes, Mrs. Maxwell, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Society for the Family of Man, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Society for International Development, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Spalding, Curt J, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Sparkman, John J, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - State, Department of, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Straus, Donald B, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Sulzberger, Mrs. Arthur H, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Swidler, Joseph C, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Szanton, Mrs. Jules, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Szold, H. James, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Taylor, Harold, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Technology Communication, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Time (Magazine), 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Tobey, David M, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Tobey, Nancy, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Tobey, William, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Tree, Marietta, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Re Truman, Harry S. - Library Institute, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Tugwell, Rexford G, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Tyler, Carroll L, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Van Mourick, Lawrence L, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Vaughn, Jack H, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Re Vietnam, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Volpe, Joseph Jr, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Volunteers for International Development, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Wallace, Earl D, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Walp, Robert M, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Warne, W. Robert, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Webster, Bethuel M, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Wells, Herman B, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
    - Wheeler, John A, 1968; 1 box (Box 479)
  - Subseries 18J: 1969-1970, 13 boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence and related material for 1969-1970.
    - Abram, Morris B, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Re African American Dialogues (programs), 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Afshar, Yamin, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Allen, Forrest, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - American Academy of Achievement, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - American Chemical Society, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - American Committee for Assistance to Tunisia, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - American Committee for the Weizmann Institute for Science, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - American Management Association, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - American Museum of Natural History, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Anderson, Leo L, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Ansari, Abdol Reza, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Association for Voluntary Sterilization, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Atchley, Dana W, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Atlantic Council, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Re Atomic Energy, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Avant-Garde, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Backer, George, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Baker, Howard H, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Baumgartner, Leona, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Re Baumgartner, William J, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Beckerley, James G, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Re Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Berle, Adolf A, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Bernstein, Marver H, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Bingham, Mrs. Jonathan B, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Bio-Atomic Research Foundation, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Birnbaum, Harold F, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Blatchfoed, Joseph H, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Bliven, Bruce, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Bloch, Ivan, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Blond, Anthony Ltd, 1969; 1 box (Box 480)
    - Bok, Derek C, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bolton, Bennet M, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bowser, LeRoy B, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bradner, Mrs. James, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bromberger, Nancy and Sylvain, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Brooks, John, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Bush, George, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Business Abroad, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Business Council for International Understanding, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Re California University, Irvine, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Carvajal, Manuel, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Century Association, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Civil Service Commission, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Clifford, Clark M, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Coates, Albert, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Collingwood, Charles, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Re Colombia, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Re Commission on Foundations and Private Philanthropy, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Court, Chrles W, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Cousins, Norman, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Coyle, David, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Cronkite, Walter, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Curtis, Richard, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Daggett, John T., Jr, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Daniels, Jonathan, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - John Day Company Inc. Publishers, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Re DePauw University, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1969; 1 box (Box 481)
    - Diawara, Mohammed T, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Diebold, John, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Dirksen, Everett M, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Doar, John, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Douglas, Mrs. Melvyn, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Drabkin, Mrs. Israel, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Drummond, Roscoe, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Education and World Affairs, Inc. (EWA), 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Eklund, Siguard A, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Elliott, Osborn, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Engelhard Minerals and Chemicals Corporation, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Ernst, Morris L, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Evers, Charles, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Farm Journal, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Franklin Book Programs, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Franklin, John C, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Freedom House, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Fried, Walter, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Friendly, Alfred, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Fugitt, Warren 0, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Fuller, William A., Jr, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Garces Cordoba, Bernardo, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Gardner, John W, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Glick, Frank and Virginia, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Goheen, Fobert F, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Goodwin, Richard N, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Gould, Bruce and Beatrice, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Greenbaum, Edward S, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Greeneye, Mrs. Lawrence, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Gruening, Ernest, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Gunther, Johnl, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Gutierrez Atencio, Francisco J, 1969; 1 box (Box 482)
    - Haar, Charles M, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Hammond Historical Society, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Hannah, John A, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Hansen, Stephen C, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Harkens, Robert C, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Harvard Business Review, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Harvard Law School, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Herrick, H. Terry, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Hewlett, Richard G, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Hey, Don F, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Hogan, Elizabeth R, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Holifield, Chet, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Hough, Henry B, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re Hunter College Student Association, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Huntley, Chet, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Institute for Mediterranean Affairs, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - International Study Project, Inc, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re Tran, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re Iran Emergency Reconstruction and Rehabilitation Committee, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re Ivory Coast, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Japan Association for the 1970 World Exposition, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Advanced International Studies, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Johnson, Joseph E, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Julian, Percy L, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Kennedy, Edward M, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re Kennedy, Robert F. - Memorial Foundation, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Kissinger, Henry A, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Klein, Miriam, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Knight, Douglas M, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. - Publishers, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Komer, Robert W, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re LaFollette, Philip F, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lazard Freres, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lazarus, Ralph, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - League of Women Voters, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Leonhart, William, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Levin, Gerald M, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re Levitt, Arthur, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lilienthal, Allen, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Re Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lilienthal, Michael, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lindsay, John V, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lipkin, Arthur B, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lively, Robert A, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Lynagh, Paula and Vincent, 1969; 1 box (Box 483)
    - McAlister, John T., Jr, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - McCloy, John J, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - MacDonald, D.G., 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Macy, John W., Jr, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Re Martha's Vineyard, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Masire, Q.K.J., 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Mead, Thomas A, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Memphis State University, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Meyer, Armin H, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Meyner, Helen and Robert B, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Michelmore, Peter, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Moore, Hugh - Fund, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Morehouse, Edward W, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Morino, Mitsutoshi, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Re Morocco, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Morse, David A, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Morse, F. Bradford, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Murphy, Franklin D, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Murphy, Robert D, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Muskie, Edmund S, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Nathan, Robert R, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - National Book Committee, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - National Rural Electric Cooperative Association, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - New York Times, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Newsweek, 1969; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Nichols, William I, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Re Nixon, Richard M, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Re Nuclear Power Plants, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Nugent, Luci Johnson, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Oakes, John B, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Olds, Glenn A, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Oliver, John, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Re Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Ortona, Egidio, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Overseas Development Council (O.D.C.), 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Owen, Marguerite, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Oxnam, Mrs. G. Bromley, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Penalosa Camargo, Enrique, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Perkins, Milo, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Phillips, Christopher H, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Planned Parenthood/World Population, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Princeton University, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Pritchard, Ross, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Prud'homme, Hector, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Re Publications by David E. Lilienthal, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
      Includes letters regarding the Journals of David E: Lilienthal, Volume IV; Management: A Humanist Art-, 1968.
    - Re Puerto Rico, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Radcliffe College, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Raphealson, Joel, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Raytheon Education Company, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Research Institute of Japan, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Reston, James, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Robinson, William J, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Robock, Stefan H, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Rockefeller, John D. ITT, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Rogers, William P, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Rouhani, Mansour, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Re Rutgers University, 1969; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Schmidt, Benno C, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sherman, Henry, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sholes, Mrs. Maxwell, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Shriven Robert Sargent, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Re "Speaking Freely" program, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
      Includes an interview with David E. Lilienthal, March 16, 1969
    - Stanford University, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - State, Department of, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Stern, Philip M, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Re Stevenson., Adlai - Institute, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Suarez, Diego, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sulzberger, Mrs. Arthur H, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Swidler, Joseph C, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Szanton, David L, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Szanton, Jonathan, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Szanton, Victor L, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Re Tanzania National Parks, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Texas, University of: Oral History Project, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Thompson, Edward K, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Tobey, David M, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Tobey, Nancy, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Tobey, William, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Tour, Harry B, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Tree, Marietta, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Re Truman, Harry S, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Tsuji, Yutaka, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - United States Air Force Academy, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Urwick, Lyndall F, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Vadney, Thomas E, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Vahidi, Traj, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Vaughn, Jack H, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Re Vietnam, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Volpe, Joseph Jr, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Walp, Robert M, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Warne, William E, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Webb, James E, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Weiss, Carlo, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Re Weizmann Institute of Science, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Wells, Herman B, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Wessenauer, Gabriel 0, 1969; 1 box (Box 486)